Hey, idiot. Wake up, already.
It's so hot!
Time to switch to summer uniforms.
Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
The Cracked Crocus
I was so relieved about passing exams,
I let work get away from me.
Now that Enomoto-san's joined the team,
I gotta work even harder as a creator.
Like Saku-nee-san said,
I need to quit being stuck in time.
Yu!
Morning!
M-Morning.
Well played, main model!
You know my weakness!
But alas!
Oh yeah, Himari.
You check out that dog post I sent you?
Yup! Sure did!
I know you're just acting slick.
I see you eyeing my summer uniform!
Shut up.
I'm still scarred over you humiliating me
in front of the class last year.
Don't sweat it!
Everyone has a secret fetish or two.
I'm not shy about how much I love your eyes.
You tell people that?
Won't that give people the wrong idea?
Wrong idea how?
D-Dammit, she's trying to pressure me
into saying it out loud.
But I'm a changed man!
You know exactly how.
People will look at us like we're dating.
Deep down, I bet you actually
want to go out with me.
What's that look like she's
so happy she can't contain herself?
Then... what if we really went out?
What?! But we're in class—
Wait. I know what happens next.
Ow! Come on, Yu!
Stop acting rebellious like Enocchi!
Shut up.
It's not my fault you suck at romance!
So much for trying to trick me.
I wish I had a good comeback...
So what's the plan today?
Enomoto-san doesn't
have band practice today,
so I was thinking of having a team meeting.
Yu-kun, Hii-chan.
Sorry about the wait!
Man, Enocchi. Those things are lethal.
You look nice in the summer uniform.
Th-Thanks.
Crap!
"That was nothing like
your reaction to seeing me
glimmering under the bright
summer sun. You prick!"
Is that it?
U-Um, did you see my message?
About the team meeting? Yup!
Currently preparing to grow flowers!
So what's the agenda?
I think the first thing is what
to do with our inventory.
Since preserved flowers
change colors with time.
Really?
Then we should promote
them as soon as we can.
Yup! So next, we shoot promos
and post them online. Right?
R-Right, with Himari as the model.
Gee, I hope that didn't seem
like a leading question!
Whatever it was, I don't like it.
Oh, there he is!
Natsume-kun!
Hey Himari-san! And Enomoto-san!
Woah, this is a crazy good-looking group.
Hey, Mao-py and Azu-kyun! What's up?
We wanted to ask about those accessories
you promised us the other day!
Oh yeah!
Science Room
Phew.
You can take any of the ones in here.
No, that's not special enough!
We want custom ones!
I figured you might say that.
Could you start by letting
us know what you want?
Custom-made pieces can get expensive.
So you might wanna think about your budget.
And besides...
Yu decides what pieces to make.
My bad. I thought it was
the same as the other ones.
See, it's Mao and her boyfriend's
anniversary next month.
I wanted a matching pair of accessories,
but haven't been able to find any that work.
You mean you want a piece for a guy
and girl under the same concept?
Exactly!
Not a bad idea.
A matching set would be a new challenge.
Looks like Yu's up for it!
Yay!
That was exhausting.
Yu, you gotta toughen up.
Creators have to engage
with customers in this day and age!
Yeah, but those two are so outgoing.
I want customers who are a bit tamer.
Keeping notes...
"That face means Yu-kun's up for it."
Is that necessary?
So we're going to plan
something for those two,
while clearing out inventory. Sound good?
Okay!
Roger that.
About the flower for this piece...
I'm thinking the Japanese cornel.
Cornel?
Umm... This?
It represents maintenance,
resilience, and mature spirit.
But why this? Kinda has
an old lady vibe, doesn't it?
Remember when we met with that couple?
Instead of an intense love,
they gave off a tangible vibe.
The Japanese cornel is the flower of health.
If we're talking about a long,
sustainable relationship,
I thought something more
down-to-earth would suit them.
You think it's a bit too cheesy?
Don't say that.
It's ultimately up to the customer,
but we respect your vision as the creator.
Yup!
Th-Thanks.
What about the price?
That's the only hang-up...
Is there a problem?
Honestly, I think our prices right now
are too expensive for high schoolers.
Yeah, teenagers only make up
10% of our customers overall.
And we've flown under
the radar at school so far
since everything has been
sold through social media.
But there's other girls like me...
Yeah, and now that people know who you are,
you might be getting a lot more attention.
Is it bad if I get more attention?
Well what if girls—
You might get really popular with girls!
Enomoto-san, don't say dumb stuff like that.
D-Dumb...?
Sorry! It slipped out!
I reacted like I would with Himari!
That means I'm catching up
to Hii-chan, right?
You're so positive...
I guess it's not a bad thing
for customers to come to you.
Yeah.
I'll try to engage with
customers more for You's sake.
It might just be the breakthrough I need,
like Saku-nee-san said.
A Few Days Later
Wow!
I've never heard of the Japanese cornel.
But it's so pretty! Isn't it?
Yeah.
It'll look nice on you, Mao.
You think so?
Pardon me.
I'm not very good with accessories...
Senpai, you have a good frame
so I think it'll suit you.
Necklaces shouldn't be tucked away,
they need to be shown off.
Makes sense.
You know, I was a bit shy
about the matching set thing,
but she really liked the piece
she bought from you last year.
And you were so open to our thoughts, too.
Like I thought, when
people love each other...
It's just so beautiful in my eyes.
Um, I heard that you could order
custom-made accessories here?
There's a rumor going around
that you can make something perfect
to fit people and their crush.
She's the fifth person just today.
That's so many.
Looks like Mao-py and Azu-kyun
have been spreading the word.
Word-of-mouth beats any ad.
The matching set was great,
but that earring you made Azu-kyun
was really cute, too.
People have been asking me
about it in band, too.
For real?
We gotta find the time to make them.
Science Room
Wow.
You wanted a feminine,
Japanese design, right?
Thanks.
This means he'll fall for me,
like the rumors said!
Hi there!
Is it true that You's accessories will
make your crush fall in love with you?
People are getting carried away
with this made-to-order thing.
They're more willing to pay
the hiked price since
these are completely unique pieces,
unlike the ones before.
And those two are too good
at promoting this stuff!
Don't be shy!
We can totally spread
the word on how great these are!
Leave it to us!
It started as an "original" accessory.
Then it became a "one-of-a-kind
accessory made to order."
Now it's an accessory that'll "make
your romantic wishes come true."
Can't we ask them to hold off on promo?
How can we? They're so happy to do it.
You have to admit, it is nice of them.
We'll just have to power through it.
Yu! How's it going?
I'm amazed at this space
Hibari-san prepared for me.
Oh, and sorry to be here while you're out.
It's fine.
We can't leave the science room
unattended in case a new client pops in.
I appreciate it.
I can hardly get anything done
at home thanks to Daifuku.
So I might be cooped up in here for a while.
Shouldn't you get some rest?
I'll wake you up when Enocchi gets here.
What are you doing?
Inviting you to rest on my
cute little lap, of course.
You can't be stupid enough
to decline this offer.
You being cute is exactly
why I'd have to decline.
Oh well. It's not like anyone will see.
"If this were Enocchi, I bet
I wouldn't be able to see her face."
Is that what you're thinking?
O-Of course not!
Himari-san, napping on your lap is the best!
Ew, are you picking up phrases
from Makishima-kun?
Don't even think about copying that player.
Cut the crap. Let me sleep.
Himari. Can I ask you something?
Remember when I made
a piece for Enomoto-san?
You said you wanted an accessory of romance.
Oh my gosh, that's so embarrassing.
Why do you ask? You
feeling romance towards me?
Shut up. But what about you?
You had a bad experience
with Makishima's exes in middle school.
You've hated romance ever since? Even now?
Hmm...
Yup!
Then why did you ask
for a piece about romance?
Because Enocchi looked so cute in hers.
Oh... Okay.
I was afraid it meant she fell
for another guy.
I always thought I'd be fine
if Himari got a boyfriend.
But now... even if
it's just as a best friend,
I want her by my side forever.
Himari's nice enough
to do that if I ask her.
But I don't wanna take
advantage of her like that.
That's why I need to work
harder... to be her equal...
I wonder if it's because
he's been so focused on work.
Yu's clearly changed.
Before, all he needed
was to satisfy himself.
But now, his eyes are burning with passion.
He gives me goosebumps now.
And it scares me at the same time.
Like he might leave me
and go off on his own.
I hate romance.
Thanks to all these girls caught up in love,
I've had less time with Yu recently.
What a drag.
I don't need a piece about romance.
As long as I have this best friend ring,
Yu will stay by my side.
But if anyone were to ask
if I wanted to go back
to the days when we were only friends...
My answer would be "no."
Because if I never realized that I loved Yu,
I wouldn't have known
the happiness I do now.
I'm probably living the happiest
days of my life right now.
I'm not exaggerating. It's true.
So we're delivering two pieces today.
Let's break up into groups
so we can deliver these—
I thought I saw a guy
with some gorgeous girls.
And what do you know? It's Natsu!
Hey, Makishima-kun. Can we help you?
You don't have to copy her, Enomoto-san.
Remember, Rin-chan.
Too much physical contact
makes it less special.
Save that for the right moment
to leave an impression.
Oh! Right!
Don't make note of that.
Rin-chan sure makes a great student.
She'll beat out Himari-chan
in no time, don't you worry.
You know, Makishima-kun.
Instead of focusing
on other people's love lives,
you should make sure your younger
girlfriend doesn't get fed up of you.
More importantly, Natsu.
Wanna grab a bite to eat?
I thought we could discuss
the future of You.
Did you put those two up
to promoting my accessories?
Nope, that was entirely their choice.
They may be part of the popular crowd,
but they're friendly
with any circle of students.
They love being in other people's business
but act purely on good intentions.
Yeah?
That's why they were the perfect pair
to help leak the creator of You.
What do you mean?
Even 100% good intentions can
sometimes turn into 200% ill intentions.
I have no clue what you're talking about.
I wanted to talk to you
to apologize beforehand.
If everything goes as expected,
you might be in for some emotional pain.
What? Why would you do that?
For Rin-chan, of course.
I'm totally lost.
Why are you so invested
in helping Enomoto-san anyways?
Because I owe Rin-chan.
Something worth way more than
helping her realize her first love.
It wasn't long before I found out
the full scope of Makishima's plans.
Did you make this?
Y-Yes...
We received a complaint from the parents
of the female student who bought this.
A complaint?
They say their daughter was coerced
into buying this accessory for a high price.
That's not what happened at all!
We made this based on her requests
and shared the price in advance.
She agreed to it.
Is there proof of that?
Only a statement of delivery and receipt...
But that's with Himari.
Okay then. I'll ask Inuzuka about that.
By the way, are your handmade
accessories sold according to regulations?
O-Our accessories are accounted under
my family's convenience store business.
We've undergone legal processes,
and my sister manages that side.
That's right, your sister's Sakura.
You've been a handful with your blank exams.
But Sakura was a handful for being so smart.
I'll have to discuss
with the other teachers first,
but even if the school determines
your activities are no issue,
the same can't be said
for other parents who don't know you.
All they know is that their kid bought
an expensive accessory.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
I won't tell you to stop making them.
But you'll have to pause sales
for the time being.
Any orders you've already
accepted will have to wait. Okay?
What? That's ridiculous!
She sounds like a Karen in the making!
Thankfully, Sasaki-sensei
did some damage control.
We're lucky to get off this easy.
But we'll have to assert ourselves more.
She's the one lying, after all.
Man, that was such a waste of money.
We only did it cause Senpai told us to.
Exactly!
So dumb!
I only bought that expensive thing because
they promised it would
make him like me back!
You think we can return it?
So I can admit to them I got dumped? No way.
I bet it's all to make more money.
I hate Senpai for dumping me.
And whoever spread that rumor.
And that guy who made this!
They can all go to hell!
She said she had a crush
on another senpai from her club.
She wanted a feminine,
Japanese-style piece he would like.
Seeing her talk about her love for him...
I thought it was beautiful
how innocent and giddy she looked.
Hey!
A lot of work went into that!
Why would you do something like that?!
Let me go!
It's not worth it! Let's go!
Having feelings for someone
is a beautiful thing.
Like how I realized my feelings for Himari,
and how that motivated me
to be a better person.
But "beautiful" doesn't always mean "pure."
Yu-kun...
She was right.
Even something
as beautiful as loving someone
doesn't necessarily mean
their intentions are pure.
Realizing that made me feel...
like a huge piece of shit.
Zinnia and Where Passion Lies